task. What I mean to say is like, "Oh,
you're you're holding four boxes and
someone is coming up to you and says, "I
have a cart available for you to carry
these boxes. Do you want this cart?" And
it's like, "My car is 10 ft away." And
it's like, "Well, but think about
all of the times that you're carrying
this 10 ft thing." You should you should
minimize further because who knows what
other bird you might need to carry
another box next time you're anyway I
feel like that's we brain
I'm not saying brainwash but we
add reward functions to our decisions
which are mainly
seemingly
cost minimization engines. Okay. And
when we're in an environment where our